question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science: Mathematics",
        "question": "E = MC3",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the Monster Hunter Series, G-Rank is the highest possible prestige a Hunter can recieve.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Books",
     "question": "Dracula is destroyed by contact with sunlight", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Computers",
                                      "question": "All program codes have to be compiled into an executable file in "
                                                  "order to be run. This file can then be executed on any machine.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Antarctica is the largest desert in the world.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
                                       "question": "The two atomic bombs dropped on Japan by the United States in "
                                                   "August 1945 were named &#039;Little Man&#039; and &#039;Fat "
                                                   "Boy&#039;.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Art",
     "question": "Leonardo da Vinci&#039;s Mona Lisa does not have eyebrows.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
                                       "question": "There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The Kerbol System (from Kerbal Space Program) includes a Saturn analogue.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
